Christjan Kinasch

Software & Applications Developer

Contact

About

Email

c.kinasch@gmail.com

Mobile

0432 345 241

Portfolio

christjankinasch.github.io

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/ christjankinasch/

Skills

Java

Cross platform mobile applications

Dart, Flutter

Web technologies

PHP, Node | React, ASP

Data processing

Python, Jupyter, Pandas, Spark

Version control

git, github

Windows Server 2016

Tertiary graduate of **Information Technology** with strong written, and verbal communication skills, as well as experience in: writing technical documentation, and the development life cycle from concept to completion.

Education

Advanced Diploma of Information Technology

The Gordon, Geelong | 2019

Cert IV of Information Technology

The Gordon, Geelong | 2018 | Cert of Excellency

Cert III of Information Technology

North Metro Tafe, Perth | 2017

Trade Cert III of Commercial Cookery

The Gordon, Geelong | 2014-2016

Employment

Sous Chef

Valley Inn Hotel, Geelong | 2017-2018

- Co-ordination of daily operations
- Assisting development of operational standards to ensure client satisfaction
- Inventory management

Apprentice Chef

Various locations, Geelong | 2014-2016

- Affecting a professional discipline
- Integrating into an established hierarchy
- Refining an efficient work flow pattern